Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/khoi-nguyenxuan-minh-137577163 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data as a Service (DaaS)
Private Clouds
Virtualization

Languages

Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter Tuning, Regularization and Optimization

Python 3 Tutorial course

Structuring Machine Learning Projects

Microsoft Certified: Azure Al Fundamentals

Dataiku ML Practitioner

Khoi Nguyen Xuan Minh

Al Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I was an engineer who graduated from Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology with a degree in Telecommunications Engineering before dabbling in data science and analytics.

Working as an engineer in college gives me opportunities to access and adapt to many kinds of incredible technologies. However, deep down, my passion lies in discovering insights from datasets and understanding the behavior in order to make more significant and more practical applications in any industry that I'm working on. I have experience and expertise in:

- Advanced Python Programming, Data Analytics, and Practical Statistics such as OOP, JSON, SQL, Regex, Naive Bayes, Regression, Multiple Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, and Data Visualization.
- Good knowledge in Machine Learning and Deep Learning such as SVM, Random Forest, XGBoost, Clustering, Text Mining, Computer Vision, and Natural Language Processing.

Experience

Phalanx Services Co.,Ltd
Al Engineer
June 2023 - Present (1 year 10 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Algorithmics Vietnam
Programming Teacher
September 2022 - April 2024 (1 year 8 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

FPT Software Data Scientist

April 2022 - June 2023 (1 year 3 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

FPT Telecom

2 years 11 months

Data Scientist

June 2021 - April 2022 (11 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Data Analyst

November 2019 - June 2021 (1 year 8 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Data Analyst

June 2019 - October 2019 (5 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

VUS - The English Center

Teaching Assistant

May 2018 - April 2020 (2 years)

Vietnam

Education

FPT University

Master of Software Engineering, Data Analytics · (2021 - 2023)

Udacity

Nano Degree, Data Analyst · (September 2022 - October 2022)

Udacity

Nano Degree, Data Engineer · (August 2022 - September 2022)

Udacity

Nanodegree, Data Scientist · (May 2022 - August 2022)

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology

Bachelor's Degree (in English), Electrical and Electronics

Engineering · (2015 - 2020)